(upbeat music)
(upbeat music continues)
♪ Rising up, back on the street ♪
♪ Did my time, took my chances ♪
♪ Went the distance, now
I'm back on my feet ♪
♪ Just a man and his will to survive ♪
♪ So many times it happens too fast ♪
♪ You change your passion for glory ♪
♪ Don't lose your grip on
the dreams of the past ♪
♪ You must fight just to keep them alive ♪
♪ It's the eye of the tiger ♪
♪ It's the thrill of the fight ♪
♪ Rising up to the
challenge of our rival ♪
♪ And the last known survivor
stalks his prey in the night ♪
♪ And he's watching us all
with the eye of the tiger ♪
(upbeat music)
♪ Face to face, out in the heat ♪
♪ Hanging tough, staying hungry ♪
♪ They stack the odds 'til
we take to the street ♪
♪ For the kill with the skill to survive ♪
♪ It's the eye of the tiger ♪
♪ It's the thrill of the fight ♪
♪ Rising up to the
challenge of our rival ♪
♪ And the last known survivor
stalks his prey in the night ♪
♪ And he's watching us all
with the eye of the tiger ♪
(upbeat music)
♪ Rising up straight to the top ♪
♪ Had the guts, got the glory ♪
♪ Went the distance,
now I'm not gonna stop ♪
♪ Just a man and his will to survive ♪
♪ It's the eye of the tiger ♪
♪ It's the thrill of the fight ♪
♪ Rising up to the
challenge of our rival ♪
♪ And the last known survivor
stalks his prey in the night ♪
♪ And he's watching us all with the eye ♪
♪ Of the tiger ♪
(upbeat music)
♪ The eye of the tiger ♪